<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>👋 Hi there. on Technical Founder Community</title><link>https://techfounder.community/</link><description>Recent content in 👋 Hi there. on Technical Founder Community</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://techfounder.community/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Nashville, Tennessee</title><link>https://techfounder.community/locations/nashville/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://techfounder.community/locations/nashville/</guid><description>Who runs TFC in Nashville? Brian Dailey It all started with this LinkedIn post and many discussions with local engineers. I want to see more engineers who are considering starting a company take the plunge. I wrote more about my thoughts on this here. Why Nashville? Nashville is a very collaborative community and a lot of smart engineers. The Nashville Entrepreneur Center have a corner on the MBA/suits, but the overlap between &amp;ldquo;startup biz-types&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;engineers&amp;rdquo; is pretty small.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://techfounder.community/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://techfounder.community/contact/</guid><description>The &amp;ldquo;owner&amp;rdquo; of the domain is Brian Dailey. You can reach him via this anonymized email address.</description></item><item><title>Membership</title><link>https://techfounder.community/membership/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://techfounder.community/membership/</guid><description>How can I join the group? Find your location and start the process from there (right now, just skip straight to Nashville).
What is the Code of Conduct? All group members and attendees are required to comply with the Code of Conduct.
The Short Version Be respectful of other people, respectfully ask people to stop if you are bothered; respect privacy; group leads are not paid and have day jobs, so please be respectful of their time; and if you can’t resolve an issue with someone else you should contact the admins.</description></item></channel></rss>